JAY KUNDARIYA

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

+91 79842 23426

🔽 jaykundariya786@gmail.com

Surat, Gujarat, India

LINKEDIN

Enthusiastic and motivated **React Native developer** with 3 years of experience in developing Android and iOS applications. Proven skill in working independently or as part of a team, with a focus on delivering excellent results even under tight deadlines. Excited to join a reputable company, take on challenges, bring innovation, and contribute ideas to propel projects forward.

SKILLS

- React Native
- Expo
- React Js
- Next Js
- Firebase
- Tailwind
- Project Management Tools
 (Click Up Jira Slack)
- IDE:

(VsCode - Xcode - Android Studio)

EDUCATION

COMPUTER ENGINEERING (B.E.)

Pacific school of engineering

2019 - 2023

LANGUAGE

- Gujrati
- Hindi
- English

EXPERIENCE

UNIKWORK SYSTEMS LLP

Jun 2024 - Present

 Responsible for managing tasks of the mobile app development team.

EWINGS INFOTECH

Nov 2023 - Jun 2024

- Learn new technology Next.js and Tailwind CSS.
- Created a Desktop responsive app with flex and dynamic height, width, and font size.
- Learned how to communicate with different teams to fulfill project requirements.

WEBASHLAR SOFTWARE SOLUTION PVT LTD

July 2022 - Nov 2023

- Responsible for managing tasks of the mobile development team.
- Ensure the performance, quality, and responsiveness of the app.
- Created tablet and T.V. responsive user experience with flex and dynamic height, width, and font size.

PORTFOLIO

JAPA HEALTH

- The application is based on health and meditation to control the mind and body.
- In this project, I created a video controller and theme-based animation model.
- This application connects doctors and users (normal people) who register it's self.

SMS MARKETING APP

- This application is based on sending and receiving text messages directly on the application.
- Create a native module for sending and receiving text messages.
- Send a common message to 100+ contacts in every 1 sec.

SHEIHEK

- This application is based on a music player platform.
- Create a music player controller, manage the queue, and repeat the song.
- Dark mode and Light mode are also available.
- Also, create a local data store to save favorite songs and user information.

MAX DEAL

- This application is based on a hotel and hotel facility booking application.
- PLAY STORE

STORY WELL

- This application is based on a daily dairy and daily news application.
- PLAY STORE

THAT GUYS GARAGE LLC

- This application is based on a range of counts of your performance, So remember it.
- PLAY STORE

QTAH

- This application is based on a car modification part supply.
- This app had three faces one for user, second for supplier, and three for driver.
- Dark mode and Light mode are also available.
- Also, a localization in Arabic and English language.